# Marco Antonio V Montoya



Mexican



October 6th 1989



Montreal Canada



+1(514)209 5032



marcovmontoya.me



MarcoVMontoya1989



marcovmontoya@gmail.com

### PROFILE

Professional developer with 5 years of experience in web development, specialized in ReactJS, JavaScript frameworks. Always combining my passion for programming & technology I'm a self-driven person, committed to achieving results, with keen eye for details, looking for the best solution to problems with best code practices.

#### EXPERIENCE

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER FRONTEND, Mexico City

JUNE 2017 - APRIL 2019 linio com mx

Working in Frontend and Backend team in charge to create new features to improve, integrate the content and new features of the website, debugging and improving the UI experience, improving API for mobile team, creating new features to have impact on purchaces, reviewing code form other developers, unit test, also I worked for other clients to maintain Hewlett Packard, Banco Pacifico (Ecuador), Club Premier, Avianca Lifemiles using the Linio template.

# WINDOWS AZURE CONSULTANT & DEVELOPER, Mexico City OCTOBER 2015 - NOVEMBER 2016 CLOUD CONTINUITY SYSTEMS SERVICES

Responsible of developing web pages (mainly web design with C# and ASP.NET) to implement the Cloud Services using Azure Websites Services API.

### INTERN CONSULTANT AND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, Mexico City

August 2014 - February 2015 CLOUD CONTINUITY SYSTEMS SERVICES

Responsible in the participation of CSP projects with Azure in the creation of demos from Azure Portal.

### EDUCATION

CDI College Montreal - Web Design and Programming College Degree. August 2019 - February 2021

Panamerican University Mexico - Project Management.

Bachelor of Engineering Project Management. August 2014 - July 2015

Panamerican University Mexico - Information Technology and Intelligen Systems Engineer

Bachelor of Engineering. August 2009 - July 2014

### SKILLS

JavaScript	React JS	Git	CSS	Photoshop
PHP	Redux	Bootstrap	SASS	Illustrator
TDD	Symphony	Styled-Components	HTML5	
OOP	MySQL	Tailwind	NodeJS	

### OTHER/ HOBBY

VideoGames, Cinema, Books, Swimming, Trading Cards Game, Board Game, Dogs. I use Cochelar Implant